Hello Hello friends, welcome once again to
your channel Trading and if you are
new to the channel then subscribe to the channel
because I keep bringing such great videos
and I bring videos of the stocks which are also
on the market level. If I
talk about today's stock then
today's line is ICICI Lombard, it is a very
good company, I like
ICICI General Insurance a lot. If we talk about the
market cap, it has a market
cap of 67,000. If we talk about Daniel, there is no special deal,
district wise four and this is
also about mylife test, but it is
expensive behind the industry, the delivery is quite good, return is
70% and brother, let's talk about its one
year return, it is 11% return in one year, it is
not a very special return, but still I find the
company okay. If we talk about long
term returns, then the company has just been listed, it got listed
this year something, it was
listed in September 17 and has a
return of 121%, so it has made a big part of
your money, it has made one lakh
rupees there.  2 lakh 21 thousand rupees is a
decent return, it's not that much, it's
not even right, I think it's okay, the
rest of the returns are so much, let's talk about the
company's quarterly results, the
results were decent, you can see the opinion was the
same, brother, brother, and brother, and the
results were decent, and let's talk about the
shareholding pattern, 151 percent,
in this the promoter holding is quite good, the mutual fund has a
holding of 10.53 percent, and FIR has a
very good holding, they are
sitting with the goods, the entire direct pass is
not a special building, it is 1.5-2% and the
retail is full inside, this point note
4, let's talk about the cent polling, and the
financial growth of the company is quite
excellent, so you can see it year after year,
you can check it, I found
its growth to be quite good, the rest you pass and
read, let's talk about the
price to buy on the chart, so today I had given you an opportunity to
buy in the range of 1450, and I was going to
tell you that you get  This
too, between 1480 and 1450, you can place a BT
and it has shown some recovery.
Now, there is an
opportunity again. You
can buy something positive between 1414 and 50,
50 or 20-25 fennel, whatever according to your bull.
And if it goes further down, then
its second support or
something of 1200, you have to add more quantity there. And if it
goes then it is fine, if it does not go then I will
just tell you here, it is a good thing. And
similarly, this roti 6, that here it had become barrel,
MS Word has roasted the signal line, that is
where the bottom has become officer, so there
may be a fall and you can see it,
from here you can consolidate, so you can see
brother,
if it comes on the second support which I have told you, then you have to buy on
that, otherwise you
can buy on this page also. If it gets between 1480 and 1450, then you
can buy there. If you want to do
some quantity and short term trading, then
also  You can take it and
if you like the video then like the video
and subscribe to the channel and
share the channel with your friends, Jai Hind
friends.